umain30.com 2013-06-07

# Privacy policy of Perfect Bloggerstech

#### Perfect BloggersTech is using open source matrials and data those are have no copy right to any individuals or corporate.If you have found any such thing , don’t hesitate  to inform us via contact us page.We will immediately remove such materials or data.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Perfect BloggersTech collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://umain30.com](http://umain30.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Perfect BloggersTech.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate or phone number voluntarily submit such information to us for future interaction.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Perfect BloggersTech may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include our latest news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How we protect your information**

Your email or any other data will not share with any third except it is asked from legal authority .

## **Social Sharing and other advertising policy :-**

**Our maximum services are free of cost , so any one can share any data /information on any where with out permission but must give the proper credit to us.**

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Perfect BloggersTech has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and send you an email. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  

Ward no-2 ,

Barpeta road ,

Assam, India

pin- 781315

Mail id : umain30@umain30.com

### N.B:-This document was last updated on September 22, 2012.
